Guide to the Rice University athletic records, 1912-2010 (UA 155) UA 155
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series XIII: Addendum 6: 1932-2020 (Boxes 179-188)
  - Sub-Series L: Mini DV
    - Rice vs. Vanderbilt (4 tapes), 2009-09-26 (Box 187)
    - Rice vs. Tulsa (4 tapes), 2009-10-03 (Box 187)
    - Rice vs. Tulsa, 2009-10-03 (Box 187)
    - Rice vs. East Carolina University (4 tapes), 2009-10-07 (Box 187)
    - Rice vs. Navy (4 tapes), 2009-10-10 (Box 187)
    - Rice vs. University of Florida (4 tapes), 2009-10-21 (Box 187)
    - Rice vs. Tulane (4 tapes), 2009-11-14 (Box 187)
    - Rice vs. UTEP (4 tapes), 2009-11-21 (Box 187)
    - Billy Bob Tyrone (3 tapes), 2009 (Box 187)
    - Rice vs. UAB, 2009 (Box 187)
    - Track C-USA Championships, 2009 (Box 187)
    - Weight room, 2009 (Box 187)
    - Clement V. Dillard (Box 187)
    - Dixon (Box 187)
    - O.J. Brigance interviews (Box 187)
    - Rice vs. Marshall (Box 187)
    - Rice vs. Texas Tech (Box 187)
    - Rice vs. University of Houston (4 tapes) (Box 187)
    - Roost baseball (Box 187)
    - UNT replay (Box 187)
  - Sub-Series M: DVDs
    - Rice University highlights, 1957 (Box 187)
    - Men's Basketball Rice vs. Baylor, 1970-02-07 (Box 187)
    - Rice University highlights, 1972-1975 (Box 187)
    - Rice vs. TCU; Rice vs. Texas Tech, 1981-10-10-1981-10-17 (Box 187)
    - Rice vs. Texas, 2002-09-16 (Box 187)
    - Rice Defense vs. Houston, 2003-08-30 (Box 187)
    - Rice Kicking vs. Houston, 2003-08-30 (Box 187)
    - Rice Offense vs. Houston, 2003-08-30 (Box 187)
    - Rice Defense vs. Duke, 2003-09-13 (Box 187)
    - Rice Kicking vs. Duke, 2003-09-13 (Box 187)
    - Rice Offense vs. Duke, 2003-09-13 (Box 187)
    - Rice Defense vs. Texas, 2003-09-20 (Box 187)
    - Rice Kicking vs. Texas, 2003-09-20 (Box 187)
    - Rice Offense vs. Texas, 2003-09-20 (Box 187)
    - Rice Defense vs. Hawaii, 2003-09-27 (Box 187)
    - Rice Kicks vs. Hawaii, 2003-09-27 (Box 187)
    - Rice Offense vs. Hawaii, 2003-09-27 (Box 187)
    - Rice Defense vs. San Jose State, 2003-10-04 (Box 187)
    - Rice Kicks vs. San Jose State, 2003-10-04 (Box 187)
    - Rice Offense vs. San Jose State, 2003-10-04 (Box 187)
    - Rice Defense vs. Nevada, 2003-10-18 (Box 187)
    - Rice Kicks vs. Navy, 2003-10-18 (Box 187)
    - Rice Offense vs. Navy, 2003-10-18 (Box 187)
    - Rice Defense vs. Fresno State, 2003-10-25 (Box 187)
    - Rice Kicks vs. Fresno State, 2003-10-25 (Box 187)
    - Rice Offense vs. Fresno St., 2003-10-25 (Box 187)
    - Rice Defense vs. Nevada, 2003-11-01 (Box 187)
    - Rice Kicks vs. Nevada, 2003-11-01 (Box 187)
    - Rice Offense vs. Nevada, 2003-11-01 (Box 187)
    - Rice Defense vs. Tulsa, 2003-11-08 (Box 187)
    - Rice Kicks vs. Fresno State, 2003-11-08 (Box 187)
    - Rice Offense vs. Tulsa, 2003-11-08 (Box 187)
    - Rice Defense vs. SMU, 2003-11-15 (Box 187)
    - Rice Kicks vs. SMU, 2003-11-15 (Box 187)
    - Rice Offense vs. SMU, 2003-11-15 (Box 187)
    - Rice Defense vs. UTEP, 2003-11-22 (Box 187)
    - Rice Kicks vs. UTEP, 2003-11-22 (Box 187)
    - Rice Offense vs. UTEP, 2003-11-22 (Box 187)
    - Rice Defense vs. Louisiana Tech, 2003-11-29 (Box 187)
    - Rice Kicks vs. Louisiana Tech, 2003-11-29 (Box 187)
    - Rice Offense vs. Louisiana Tech, 2003-11-29 (Box 187)
    - Highlights for meeting, 2004-07-08 (Box 187)
    - Rice DEF vs. Houston, 2004-09-05 (Box 187)
    - Rice Kicks vs. Houston, 2004-09-05 (Box 187)
    - Rice OFF vs. Houston, 2004-09-05 (Box 187)
    - Rice Defense vs. Hawaii, 2004-09-18 (Box 187)
    - Rice Offense vs. Hawaii, 2004-09-18 (Box 187)
    - Houston, Hawaii highlights, 2004-09-20 (Box 187)
    - Rice Athletics PBS documentary, 2004-10-18 (Box 187)
    - Black tie cocktail hour, 2004 (Box 187)
    - Football banquet, 2004 (Box 187)
    - Football - Rice vs. UTEP (2 DVDs), 2004 (Box 187)
    - QB Club Navy, 2004 (Box 187)
    - QB Club SMU, Nevada, 2004 (Box 187)
    - QB Club Tulsa, 2004 (Box 187)
    - QB Club UTEP, 2004 (Box 187)
    - Rice DEF vs. Navy, 2004 (Box 187)
    - Rice DEF vs SMU, 2004 (Box 187)
    - Rice Defense vs. Fresno State, 2004 (Box 187)
    - Rice Defense vs. Nevada, 2004 (Box 187)
    - Rice Defense vs. SJS, 2004 (Box 187)
    - Rice Defense vs. Texas, 2004 (Box 187)
    - Rice Defense vs. Tulsa, 2004 (Box 187)
    - Rice Kicks vs. Fresno State, 2004 (Box 187)
    - Rice Kicks vs. Hawaii, 2004 (Box 187)
    - Rice Kicks vs. Navy, 2004 (Box 187)
    - Rice Kicks vs. Nevada, 2004 (Box 187)
    - Rice Kicks vs. SJS, 2004 (Box 187)
    - Rice Kicks vs. SMU, 2004 (Box 187)
    - Rice kicks vs. SMU, 2004 (Box 187)
    - Rice Kicks vs. Texas, 2004 (Box 187)
    - Rice Kicks vs. Tulsa, 2004 (Box 187)
    - Rice OFF vs. Louisiana Tech, 2004 (Box 187)
    - Rice OFF vs. Navy, 2004 (Box 187)
    - Rice Offense vs. Fresno State, 2004 (Box 187)
    - Rice Offense vs. Nevada, 2004 (Box 187)
    - Rice Offense vs. SJS, 2004 (Box 187)
    - Rice Offense vs. SMU, 2004 (Box 187)
    - Rice Offense vs. Texas, 2004 (Box 187)
    - Rice Offense vs. Tulsa, 2004 (Box 187)
    - Rice student athletes, 2004 (Box 187)
    - Rice vs. Hawaii, 2004 (Box 187)
    - Rice vs. Tulsa, 2004 (Box 187)
    - Ken Hatfield sports profiles PBS, 2005-03-30 (Box 187)
    - Student quotes, Houston/Campus undergrad version, 2005-08-10 (Box 187)
    - Rice vs. Houston, 2006-09-02 (Box 187)
    - Rice vs. UCLA, 2006-09-09 (Box 187)
    - Rice vs. Texas, 2006-09-16 (Box 187)
    - Rice vs. Florida State, 2006-09-23 (Box 187)
    - Rice vs. UAB, 2006-10-14 (Box 187)
    - Rice vs. ECU, 2006-11-18 (Box 187)
    - Home Depot College Football Awards Show, 2006-12-07 (Box 187)
    - Rice vs. Troy - New Orleans Bowl, 2006-12-22 (Box 187)
    - Football highlight video, 2006 (Box 187)
    - Highlights, 2006 (Box 187)
    - Highlight video, 2006 (Box 187)
    - Texas Run Out, 2006 (Box 187)
    - Rice Kicks vs Nicholls State, 2007-09-01 (Box 187)
    - Rice DEF vs. Texas Tech OFF, 2007-09-15 (Box 187)
    - Rice vs. Texas Tech, 2007-09-15 (Box 187)
    - Rice vs. Texas (3 DVDs), 2007-09-22 (Box 187)
    - Rice OFF vs. USM DEF, 2007-10-03 (Box 187)
    - Rice vs. University of Houston (2 DVDs), 2007-10-13 (Box 187)
    - Football banquet, 2007 (Box 187)
    - Rice returning player highlights, 2007 (Box 187)
    - Highlight video, 2008-01-18 (Box 187)
    - C-USA Football - Rice vs. SMU (2 DVDs), 2008-08-29 (Box 187)
    - Rice vs. Memphis, 2008-09-06 (Box 187)
    - Rice vs. Texas (3 DVDs), 2008-09-20 (Box 187)
    - Rice vs. UNT (3 DVDs), 2008-09-27 (Box 187)
    - C-USA Football - Rice vs. Tulsa (2 DVDs), 2008-10-04 (Box 187)
    - C-USA Football - Rice vs. Marshall (3 DVDs), 2008-11-22 (Box 187)
    - C-USA Football - Rice vs. Houston, 2008-11-29 (Box 187)
    - Rice Lineman Dance - Rodeo Bowl, 2008-12-27 (Box 187)
    - Texas Bowl - Rice vs. W. Michigan, 2008-12-30 (Box 187)
    - C-USA basketball tournament, 2008 (Box 187)
    - Dinner highlight, Rodeo Bowl, Season hilight, Billy Bob and Tyrone, 2008 (Box 187)
    - Night of Owl Banquet, 2008 (Box 187)
    - Regular season highs, 2008 (Box 187)
    - Rice vs. Army, 2008 (Box 187)
    - Rice vs. Houston (2 DVDs), 2008 (Box 187)
    - Rice vs. Marshall, 2008 (Box 187)
    - Pro Day, 2009-03-26 (Box 187)
    - Rice vs. UAB, 2009-09-05 (Box 187)
    - Rice vs. OSU, 2009-09-19 (Box 187)
    - Rice vs. Vanderbilt, 2009-09-26 (Box 187)
    - Rice vs. ECU (2 DVDs), 2009-10-17 (Box 187)
    - Billy Bob and Tyrone, 2009 (Box 187)
    - New recruits, 2009 (Box 187)
    - All sports loop (Box 187)
    - Army HL Loop (Box 187)
    - Billy Bob ad Tyrone with special guest (Box 187)
    - Chase and JD tribute video (Box 187)
    - Coach David Bailiff - Football camp (Box 187)
    - C-USA TV (Box 187)
    - C-USA - Bowl, C-USE, Men's BB (Box 187)
    - DJ (Box 187)
    - ESPN top 10 (Box 187)
    - Fantasy camp (Box 187)
    - Highlight video (Box 187)
    - NEL network and O.J. Brigance (Box 187)
    - Night of the Owl (Box 187)
    - Night of the Owl banquet (Box 187)
    - Pre-UH weekly highs (Box 187)
    - QB Club Texas, SIS (Box 187)
    - R (Box 187)
    - Recruit DVD (Box 187)
    - Rice DEF vs. Houston OFF (Box 187)
    - Rice DEF vs. Marshall OFF (Box 187)
    - Rice DEF vs. Memphis OFF (Box 187)
    - Rice DEF vs. Nicholls State OFF (Box 187)
    - Rice DEF vs. SMU OFF (Box 187)
    - Rice DEF vs. Texas OFF (Box 187)
    - Rice DEF vs. Tulane OFF (Box 187)
    - Rice DEF vs. Tulsa OFF (Box 187)
    - Rice DEF vs. USM OFF (Box 187)
    - Rice football office (3 DVDs) (Box 187)
    - Rice Kicks vs. Baylor (Box 187)
    - Rice Kicks vs. Houston (Box 187)
    - Rice Kicks vs. Marshall (Box 187)
    - Rice Kicks vs. Memphis (Box 187)
    - Rice Kicks vs. SMU (Box 187)
    - Rice Kicks vs. Texas (Box 187)
    - Rice Kicks vs. Texas Tech (Box 187)
    - Rice Kicks vs. Tulane (Box 187)
    - Rice Kicks vs. Tulsa (Box 187)
    - Rice Kicks vs. USM (Box 187)
    - Rice OFF vs. Baylor DEF (Box 187)
    - Rice OFF vs. Houston DEF (Box 187)
    - Rice OFF vs. Marshall DEF (Box 187)
    - Rice OFF vs. Memphis DEF (Box 187)
    - Rice OFF vs. SMU DEF (Box 187)
    - Rice OFF vs. Texas DEF (Box 187)
    - Rice OFF vs. Texas Tech DEF (Box 187)
    - Rice OFF vs. Tulsa DEF (Box 187)
    - Rice offensive line drills (Box 187)
    - Rice University football (2 DVDs) (Box 187)
    - Rice vs. Nicholls State (Box 187)
    - Rice vs. SMU (Box 187)
    - Rice vs. Texas (Box 187)
    - Rice vs. Troy (Box 187)
    - The RG and JC Show - Texas Relays (Box 187)
    - R Loop (Box 187)
    - UNT Great Outdoors (Box 187)
    - Volleyball highlight banquet video (Box 187)
    - Women's basketball - Rice vs. Georgia (2 DVDs) (Box 187)
  - Sub-Series N: Computer disks
    - Floppy disks (3), 2000 (Box 188)
    - Zip disks (25) (Box 188)
    - Rice vs. Army (CD), 2001-08-31 (Box 188)
    - Humber - Rice (CD), 2002 (Box 188)
    - Men's basketball - Rice vs. Houston (CD), 2002 (Box 188)
    - Soccer stuff (CD), 2002 (Box 188)
    - Super Regional, CWS shots (CD), 2002 (Box 188)
    - Women's soccer - Space City Shootout (CD), 2002 (Box 188)
    - Athlete mugs (CD), 2002-2003 (Box 188)
    - Sports, Action, Coach, Administrators photographs and Team and Conference Logos (CD), 2002-2003 (Box 188)
    - Men's Golf WAC Championship (CD), 2003-04-28-2003-04-30 (Box 188)
    - Arthur Culver, J.R. Harrison, Christian Kollik (CD), 2003 (Box 188)
    - Asst. Football coaches families and Mayor's cup photo (CD), 2003 (Box 188)
    - Baseball action (CD), 2003 (Box 188)
    - Evans (CD), 2003 (Box 188)
    - Football at Fresno (CD), 2003 (Box 188)
    - Football media guide (CD), 2003 (Box 188)
    - Mike Walton (CD), 2003 (Box 188)
    - Soccer guide (CD), 2003 (Box 188)
    - Rice Soccer Media Guide (2 CDs), 2003 (Box 188)
    - Rice Baseball (CD), 2004-02-05 (Box 188)
    - Coca-classic @ Rice (CD), 2004-02-20-2004-02-22 (Box 188)
    - Lamar, TSU, baseball (CD), 2004-06-05 (Box 188)
    - Rice vs. Texas A&M photographs (CD), 2004-06-06 (Box 188)
    - Awards (CD), 2004 (Box 188)
    - Baseball - regional 3 (CD), 2004 (Box 188)
    - Baseball regional (CD), 2004 (Box 188)
    - Regional (CD), 2004 (Box 188)
    - Soccer mugs (CD), 2004 (Box 188)
    - Various baseball (CD), 2004 (Box 188)
    - Women's soccer pictures (CD) (Box 188)
    - Rice '49 Team 55th Reunion, Weatherly reception (CD), 2004-10-2005-01 (Box 188)
    - Baseball - Rice vs. Texas A&M (CD), 2005-04-13 (Box 188)
    - Baseball - Rice vs. Fresno State (2 CDs), 2005-04-29 (Box 188)
    - Baseball coaches mugs (CD), 2005 (Box 188)
    - Baseball - Rice vs. Nevada (CD), 2005 (Box 188)
    - College Classic - Rice vs. Baylor (CD), 2005 (Box 188)
    - College Classic - Rice vs. Texas A&M (CD), 2005 (Box 188)
    - Minute Maid Park photographs (CD), 2005 (Box 188)
    - Rice Football - Allen Eggert retires, Coach Knodel (CD), 2005 (Box 188)
    - All pictures from golf tournament (CD), 2006-04 (Box 188)
    - Golf tournament pictures (CD), 2006-04 (Box 188)
    - Baseball (CD) (Box 188)
    - Baseball - regional 2 (CD) (Box 188)
    - Basketball exhibition (CD) (Box 188)
    - Basketball - Rice vs. Baylor (CD) (Box 188)
    - EPS (CD) (Box 188)
    - John Baseball sections (CD) (Box 188)
    - Men's basketball - Rice vs. UH (CD) (Box 188)
    - Minute Maid team photo (CD) (Box 188)
    - Rice Baseball (CD) (Box 188)
    - Rice Baseball - 36 pages and cover (CD), 1777 (Box 188)
    - Rice WAC logos (CD) (Box 188)
    - Rice Women's Swimming vs. Texas (CD) (Box 188)
    - Soccer stuff - Shockley (CD), 1777 (Box 188)
    - Standard section (CD) (Box 188)
    - Trophies (CD), 1777 (Box 188)
    - Unlabeled (CD) (Box 188)
  - Sub-Series O: Memorabilia
    - Cross pens (2) (Box 188)
    - Men's and Women's Watches (23), 1982-2002 (Box 188)